export const quiz = {
    "start_title": `Hmmm… Young one, a challenge for your mind, I offer.</br>
        A quiz of knowledge, in the galaxy far, far away.</br>
        Test your wisdom, will you? The stories of the Jedi, the Sith, and the Skywalkers await you.`,
    "quiz": [
        {
            "question": "Young Skywalker’s first mentor, who was he? Before the wise Kenobi, hmm?",
            "options": [
                "Qui-Gon Jinn",
                "Mace Windu",
                "Yoda",
                "Count Dooku"
            ],
            "answer": "Qui-Gon Jinn"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mysterious and small, on a swamp planet I live. Which planet, hmm, is my home?",
            "options": [
                "Tatooine",
                "Dagobah",
                "Endor",
                "Naboo"
            ],
            "answer": "Dagobah"
        },
        {
            "question": "Powerful with the Force, Anakin was. But the prophecy said, he was to bring balance. What name, did the Sith give him?",
            "options": [
                "Darth Plagueis",
                "Darth Tyranus",
                "Darth Sidious",
                "Darth Vader"
            ],
            "answer": "Darth Vader"
        },
        {
            "question": "Clone Wars, yes. A clone template, who was? The bounty hunter's name, hmm?",
            "options": [
                "Boba Fett",
                "Cad Bane",
                "Jango Fett",
                "Aurra Sing"
            ],
            "answer": "Jango Fett"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the arena of Geonosis, many Jedi fought. But the one who fought beside Padmé and Anakin, which Jedi Master was he?",
            "options": [
                "Plo Koon",
                "Mace Windu",
                "Ki-Adi-Mundi",
                "Kit Fisto"
            ],
            "answer": "Mace Windu"
        },
        {
            "question": "“Fear is the path to the dark side.” Hmm, remember this you do? In which episode, did these words I speak?",
            "options": [
                "Episode II: Attack of the Clones",
                "Episode III: Revenge of the Sith",
                "Episode I: The Phantom Menace",
                "Episode V: The Empire Strikes Back"
            ],
            "answer": "Episode I: The Phantom Menace"
        },
        {
            "question": "A podrace Anakin won, yes. The podracing track, on which planet, hmm, was it?",
            "options": [
                "Coruscant",
                "Kamino",
                "Tatooine",
                "Mustafar"
            ],
            "answer": "Tatooine"
        },
        {
            "question": "The wise and old Sith Lord who trained Sidious, his name, hmm?",
            "options": [
                "Darth Revan",
                "Darth Nihilus",
                "Darth Plagueis",
                "Darth Maul"
            ],
            "answer": "Darth Plagueis"
        },
        {
            "question": "The planet of fire and lava, where Obi-Wan and Anakin dueled, what is its name, hmm?",
            "options": [
                "Geonosis",
                "Mustafar",
                "Felucia",
                "Kashyyyk"
            ],
            "answer": "Mustafar"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Millennium Falcon’s co-pilot, not human he is. What species, hmm, is he?",
            "options": [
                "Ewok",
                "Rodian",
                "Wookiee",
                "Twi’lek"
            ],
            "answer": "Wookiee"
        }
    ]

}